

A student who studies at Catur Insan Cendekia University is active, friendly, polite, and respects others. Easily concerned with seeing people, and available to learn and grow. Has won 3 recitation competitions in 2021, served as administrator of the Informatics Engineering Student Association, became secretary of the Science and Technology Student Activity Unit, and member of the Music Student Activity Unit, and joined the Catur Insan Cendekia University student choir.

ADDRESS

Dusun Kiara Dangkak, RT 002 RW 001, Desa Sahbandar Kec. Kertajati, Kab. Majalengka 45457

+6285215527151 (Phone)

tiasutianahsutianah@gmail.com

(E-mail)

www.linkedin.com/in/tia-sutianah-24b593239/

(Linkedin)

www.instagram.com/tiatari1225/

(Instagram)

web.facebook.com/tia.moetmoe/

(facebook)

github.com/Sutianah

(Github)

CERTIFICATION

Himabis Sparkling Ramadhan & Kartini's Day

Pojok Literasi "Tren Urban Farming di Masa Pandemi"

Trend Bahasa Pemrograman

Simplify Your Day With IoT

Membuat Novel Semudah Membuat Status Facebook

Sutianah

Student

EDUCATION

2006 - 2007 (Kober Indah Jaya V)

2007 - 2013 (SDN Mekarjaya V)

2013 - 2019 (SMK Rise Majalengka)

2019 - Now (Universitas Catur Insan Cendekia)

EXPERIENCE

(2015 - 2016) Vice chairman of Paskibra SMPN 2 Ujungjaya

(2015 - 2016) Scout member of SMPN 2 Ujungjaya

(2015 - 2016) Class representative assembly member of SMPN 2 Ujungjaya

(2018 - 2019) Scout secretary of SMK Rise Majalengka

(2016 - 2019) Student council member of SMK Rise Majalengka

(2019 - 2020) Music student activity units Member of Universitas Catur Insan Cendekia

(2020 - 2021) IPTEK student activity units Member of Universitas Catur Insan Cendekia

(2020 - 2021) HIMATIF (Himpunan Mahasiswa Teknik Informatika) student activity units Members of Universitas Catur Insan Cendekia

SOFTWARE

Microsoft Office, Microsoft Word, Microsoft Excel, Microsoft PowerPoint, Visual Studio Code, Figma, Zoom, Google Drive, Google Meet

SKILL

Reliability, Communication, Problem Solving, Keuangan, Teamwork, Time Management, Leadership

COURSE

Kredensial Mikro Mahasiswa Indonesia (KMMI): Jaringan Komputer Era 4G

LANGUAGE

English, Indonesian language, Sundanese language

Powered by CakeResume